Huh? So then you don't currently have a boyfriend, Ms. Kinoshita?
Uh, that's right.
Would you want to go out sometime? Believe it or not, I'm kind of a catch.
Huh?
Get out! Who would have guessed?
Oh, how hilarious!
Hmm.
I set up this group date for you, remember?
Sorry, guess I'm not ready. I'd like to go home now.
Ms. Kinoshita, I hear that you're hooked on some game now.
What's it called?
I'm into mobile gaming, too.
Why don't we play together sometime?
Well, the thing is, it's not for smartphones.
It's actually a computer game called Forest of Savior.
Oh.
Oh, yeah. Forest.
Uh, I might have caught one of the commercials they had for it.
Yeah.
Yep.
That's where I know it from.
I saw the commercial!
Sorry.
No, wait.
Oh, that one.
Forest, right?
Uh, Saber something or other?
Get with the program. Are you even trying here?
We had a great group date going, and you wasted it tinkering with your phone.
Are you motivated or not?
Sorry. I got a text from Rudy, and I couldn't help myself.
Rudy?
Oh, right. One of my friends from Voss.
She's this girl with the most adorable avatar ever.
A girl?
Yeah. What's wrong?
How do you know for sure it's not actually some creepy old guy?
Isn't giving out your number risky?
But I really do think that she's a girl.
Whatever you say.
Anyway, I'm heading this way.
Buh-bye!
To be honest, I never gave it a second thought.
In my mind, I'm picturing her as a girl in high school.
I wonder what she's like.
Wow.
Gothic Lolita?
No, wait.
Yumekawa?
That girl.
She reminded me of Ruri Hime.
All right!
I only have afternoon classes tomorrow, so I can play to my heart's content tonight.
Oh, well, whatever.
I'm just not in a place where I'm ready for another romance yet.
Huh?
There's no one hanging out in the guild hall.
Hmm.
Oh.
It's Ruri Hime and Yamada!
Wonder what they're up to.
Maybe the three of us can go hunting together.
Let's see.
That's odd.
It doesn't seem like they've realized I'm here.
Say, doesn't this remind you of when we first started this guild?
Yeah, I guess.
Back then, it was just you and me all the time, remember?
There are so many more members these days.
But it's nice to be alone once in a while.
Having more time to live it up with everyone means there's less time to be alone with you.
Ruri's kind of missed that, you know?
Well, when it was only the two of us, it was easier getting things done.
These!
These two are...
An item!
Here's the item.
Ooh, thank you.
Alchemy skills, so convenient.
Maybe I should try and get this skill, too.
Oh, by the way.
There's another guild member here now, you know.
Hey!
It's Akanechi!
I totally missed your login alert.
Sorry, Akanechi.
What?
Don't be silly, of course you're not.
I'm all done.
I need to be somewhere, so I'm logging out.
Okay, bye, I'll give you a call later!
Call?
Right.
Ciao for now!
I hadn't thought of it before.
But Yamada never has much to do with anyone else.
Yet, he's always talking to Ruri-hime.
Could those two be...
Boyfriend and girlfriend?
Takuma and I started playing together, didn't we?
Maybe...
Yamada and Ruri-hime...
Akanechi?
You feeling down?
No, no, I'm okay, really!
I am kinda down.
But...
Why?
I don't understand.
Why can't I get those two out of my mind?
Social media, with its power to connect people from all over the world,
played a role in the movement known as the Arab Spring,
which started in North Africa.
As you can see from this example,
social media has publicly done this future.
One thing you say, creating new connections...
That's Yamada's account.
I want to take a look at it, but...
If I did that, it would be like spying on him.
Miss Kinoshita!
Huh?
Hey!
Oh, it's the guy from the group date.
What's his name again?
So you were in that class too?
Small world, huh?
I could see you fiddling with your smartphone from where I was.
No way!
Seriously?
Your name...
What's your name?
No good.
I'm drawing a blank.
By the way, after that group date, I checked out Forest of Saber.
It's a pretty popular game, huh?
I guess so.
Reading up on it made me want to try it out.
I mean, I do like games.
So many guys are into gaming.
Speaking of which, do you play FPS games?
F-what?
Do you know the pro gamer Yamada?
Oh, yeah, that Yamada, I, uh, I think I might have seen him in a commercial.
Sorry I asked.
You really like games, don't you, Miss Kinoshita?
I'm not sure why, but for some reason I've been feeling so rattled.
So listen, the guys in my club are talking about getting together to take a trip to Okinawa this summer.
Really?
That sounds fun.
Of course it'll be fun.
Having a good time is like second nature for us.
You can come too if you want, Miss Kinoshita.
Huh?
I'm pretty sure I've seen that girl before.
Thanks for waiting.
Come on, let's go.
And the hotel we always stay at has rooms with an ocean view.
I've never even had a girlfriend.
Well, it's no surprise with how good-looking Yamada is.
Why wouldn't he have a girlfriend or two, right?
It makes sense.
Miss Kinoshita?
What?
Oh, I'm headed this way, so I'll be going now.
Hey, Miss Kinoshita!
See you in class!
It makes sense.
So why is it that I feel so rattled?
Guess I'll pass on logging in tonight.
Who's that?
Momo, maybe?
Rurihime.
Oh man, what should I do?
I'm not really in the mood to play tonight.
False news?
I haven't logged in today, so no, I haven't.
A collab cafe, huh?
Ran into him IRL?
Could it be the girl I saw actually was Rurihime?
It did cross my mind that she had a real Rurihime vibe going on.
So does that mean...
Those two are...
I'm going to it?
What?
Huh?
What's that mean?
Oh...
Hmm...
Ugh!
Hmm?
Okay then, suppose I'll get ready.
To be fair, getting to meet your fellow guild members is rare.
So this is a great opportunity.
I'm gonna enjoy myself.
Let's see.
The Murata building north of the station will be to your left as you go straight and cross.
Uh-oh.
I should check the map again.
Where is it?
Ugh!
Sorry about that.
Oh no!
It was all my fault.
I'll get it for you.
I just hope your phone didn't get cracked.
Ugh!
Sorry about that.
Oh no!
It was all my fault.
I'll get it for you.
I just hope your phone didn't get cracked.
Ugh!
Sorry about that.
Oh no!
It was all my fault.
I'll get it for you.
I just hope your phone didn't get cracked.
Ugh!
Are you going to the Foss Collab Café?
Huh?
And by any chance...
Do you happen to play that game?
Since it's a pretty casual game,
I'd heard there had been a lot of ladies getting into it.
But who would have thought in a million years
someone as beautiful as you was playing?
Oh please!
You're too kind!
I'm tagging along because he said he'd show me the way.
But what if this is a new kind of hustle?
My friend and I started playing for fun one day,
but we're really into it now.
We even ended up starting our own guild together.
The game balance throughout is surprisingly well maintained,
and I love that there's no power gaps fueled by in-game purchases.
You could say the graphics are somewhat outdated,
but they're cute enough that I can live with the look.
And best of all, there's no dominant race,
which allows for some sweet diversity among the races.
Also, I just don't think any job class is better than the others.
But that's not to say one hasn't piqued my interest.
At the moment, I'm currently leaning towards the mage class.
Although I've gotta hand it to the dev team.
Every update brings a spot-on adjustment.
And thanks to guild buffs and the like,
guild battles have real meaning,
so it's perfectly designed to be party-oriented.
That's what makes in-game interactions so worthwhile.
By the same token, powering up can feel masochistic,
but there is proper speedrunning.
I can tell the devs really went out of their way
to reflect user feedback.
It's obvious they've learned from their past mistakes
and are trying to be better.
Thank goodness, he's just a gamer.
Anyway, that's my take on it.
What do you think?
Uh-huh.
Well, um...
I'm still a beginner when it comes to the game,
so I don't know nearly as much as the rest of you.
Just the other day,
I got yelled at for putting junk in the guild's storage.
That said, the guild master's been so nice to me,
so I really like my guild despite all that.
Uh...
What do you know?
You're playing that game too, Yamada?
Let's go one-on-one sometime!
Sure.
Yamada!
Long time no see!
Yeah, it's been a while.
Things going okay?
Fine, I'd say.
Fine, huh?
huh and you must be dirty am i right nice to meet you you look just like your character so
I knew who you were right away thanks for your text this morning I can't quite put my finger
on it but she seems a little different than she is in game so yeah what's going on here who is this
Eta I have a hunch oh you're okanachi aren't you
this watch on y'all
now
get to the right
not
already
now
me
back
hand
know
and
I
Uh, so would you guys like to go inside now?
Finally, made it.
She's freaking heavy.
I'm exhausted.
Oh, crap.
What's with the late arrival? Where were you, dude? We're all waiting on you.
Sorry to keep you. It's just that one thing led to another, and now there's a strange woman sleeping in my apartment.
Huh?
Woman? You said that right?
Unforgivable.
Woman? You said woman, right?
You all heard it, right?
Unforgivable.
Yo, which one of you is chanting that curse?
Hey, send some photos. I have to see. I swear I won't post them. You know me. I'm internet savvy.
That is not happening.
I'm your teammate. Trust me.
I don't feel so good.
Present an optical impression to us, and thy sin shall be-
Stepping away for a sec.
Hey, Yamada! Hold up!
Well, now I'm pissed. I'm gonna trash your account.
Don't do that.
Such low literacy.
Uh, are you alright?
Are you thirsty? I've got water.
No, I don't need it.
You...
Don't like me anymore.
Do you?
So just go away.
And leave me be.
Go already.
Telling me.
Telling me to go.
While clinging to me.
Isn't that a contradiction?
Seems that way.
But is that really what's going on?
I just don't get it.
Still...
If I move now...
Something tells me...
That she'll cry even harder.
She's been crying non-stop.
How miserable can she be?
It must be really rough.
This thing...
Called romance.
Please sleep peacefully till morning.
I'm gonna hurl!
I'm gonna hurl.
Cause I'm not doing.
Now-
So, if we can take you away.
Let's see what we'd like tonight.